so what's new mark how is your new job going to be honest I
complaint I really love the company that I am working for my co-workers are all really friendly and help
they really help me feel welcome it's a really energetic and fun atmosphere my boss is
and he is really flexible really how so he allows me to come in when I
and make my own hours I can also leave early if I start early there is no real dress code
I can wear jeans and a t-shirt if I want I can even wear shorts in the summer wow
sounds really cool I can't stand wearing a suit everyday which do you prefer working late
finishing early finishing early I really enjoy the morning I love getting up early and
there is nothing like watching the sunrise while drinking my morning coffee really
opposite I love sleeping in I am most the word in the evenings I am a real night
well you know what they say the early bird catches the worm
you know you could be right maybe I will try to go to bed a little earlier tonight